# Pankaj Tiwari

H.104 B Chawala, Najafgarh 9911905403 | Pankajtiwari00@yahoo.com



# **Objective**

To Secure a challenging position in a reputable organization to expand my learning, knowledge and skills, Highly Capable Marketing Manger 10 + Years of Experience leading new intiatives product awerness exponentially, performed extensive forecast, Influential growth strategist.

## **Experience**

### **Business Development Manager**

OCT 2022 - Working NIBAV ELEVATORS PVT LTD

- Work on Architects to get leads
- Mainatain architect lobby to get fresh business.
- Meeting with new Clients.
- Mainatain daily scheduled for BDE to Allocate the location to get leads (Delhi, NCR).
- Coordinate with Managment for closing strategies.
- Elevators pricing qualification
- Planning with architect to visit our plant and small gatherings.

#### **Business development Manager**

28 Oct 2020 - 30 Sep 2021 STONEX INDIA

- Managing North and west delhi Mirco Market.
- Handling Architects, Builder, contractors and High End Clients.
- Maintain relationship with Architects lobby to get bussiness on regular basis.
- Following high end sites and architect to get more business.
- Prcouring new clients through direct contact or reffrences.
- Reviewing clients feedback and implementing necessary actions.

• Remaing in tune witj trends with consumption to ensure our offerings remain relevant.

#### **Business Expansion & Market Research**

June 2017 - Sep 2020 KIXX MEDIA PVT

- Ensure Daily office operations are performed in seamless and efficient Manner.
- Managing office equipment, organizing, Arranging coordinating for Meetings.
- o Diary Management, Travel Management and Managment in Box.
- Ensuring company policies are followed
- Help to support new centre opening any pan india location.
- Visit the property inspection to get it verified as per company norms.

#### **Senior Backend Associate**

Nov 2014 - Apr 2017 MAX LIFE INSURANCE

- Handling customer queries received by Genral offices.
- Amendment according to the customer request after inspection documents.
- Maintain coordination with the otyer team to get rectified the documents.
- Receiving transactions data on daily basis and Re-organised it for analysis as per SOP.
- Coordinate with Internal team to rectify the documents.

#### **Process Associate**

Jan 2012 - SEP 2014 CSAV

- Using oracle to connect with domestic and international vendors.
- Coordinate with clients and vendors for verify to shipping Information.
- Implementing specific vendor requirments.
- Resolving vendor problem concerning codes issue.
- Monitoring ghe invoices as if we found discripancy.
- Activation and decativation of codes.
- Ensuring to resolve the discrepany within TAT.

### Relationship Officer - Amex Process

Jan 2011 - DEC 2012

**SERCO** 

- o Cross Selling to Existing and Acquisitions of new customer.
- o Provide solutions to the customer Credit card need.
- Prepare sales reports.
- o Reviews own performance and Target Accodingly on Monthly basis.
- Daily to do list to work on.

## **Education**

Course / Degree	School / University	Grade / Score	Year
BBA	Jamia Hamdard University	68%	2011
12th Class	CBSE	60%	2007
10th Class	CBSE	60%	2005

## Skills

Sales and Marketing Creative thinking Excellent communicator Techinical skills Team work \_ Target Driven Pro\_Active approach. Self Motivated

## **Interests**

**Watching Movies** 

Interaction with New people

## Languages

HINDI ENGLISH